How did this happen?
มันเกิดขึ้นได้อย่างไร?
Mythical Beast.
สัตว์ในตำนาน.
Have you seen It?
คุณเคยเห็นมันไหม
Of course. I've seen It thrice.
แน่นอน. ฉันเคยเห็นมันสามครั้ง
I've seen It 15 times.
ฉันเคยเห็นมัน 15 ครั้ง
I brought my entire family to meet It yesterday.
ฉันพาทั้งครอบครัวไปพบกับมันเมื่อวานนี้
Now that the Mythical Beast is here, this country will be in peace.
เมื่อสัตว์ในตำนานอยู่ที่นี่ ประเทศนี้จะสงบสุข
What a cheerful event.
ช่างเป็นเหตุการณ์ที่ร่าเริง
Long live, Mythical Beast.
อายุยืนยาว สัตว์ในตำนาน
Why do they think I'm the Aura?
ทำไมพวกเขาถึงคิดว่าฉันคือออร่า?
Please carry my baby.
โปรดอุ้มลูกของฉัน
Stop it. Is this a sacrifice?
หยุดนะ. นี่คือการเสียสละ?
Mythical Beast Doll, Mythical Beast Handbag and Mythical Beast Cookies.
ตุ๊กตาสัตว์ในตำนาน กระเป๋าถือสัตว์ในตำนาน และคุกกี้สัตว์ในตำนาน
The customer over there...
ลูกค้าที่นั่น...
-Why are you selling my merchandise? -Have a good look.
-ทำไมคุณถึงขายสินค้าของฉัน? - ดูดี.
But these dolls are really cute. They may be used as charms.
แต่ตุ๊กตาพวกนี้น่ารักจริงๆ อาจใช้เป็นเครื่องรางได้
What a sacred gesture.
ท่าทางศักดิ์สิทธิ์อะไรอย่างนี้
Because my figure is exquisite.
เพราะรูปร่างของฉันนั้นงดงาม
No. I'm lonely. I was lonely in my previous life as well.
ไม่ ฉันเหงา ชาติก่อนฉันก็เหงาเหมือนกัน
Up until now I'm lonely.
จนตอนนี้ฉันเหงา
I'm a lonely creature.
ฉันเป็นสิ่งมีชีวิตที่โดดเดี่ยว
The Mythical Beast is telling us something.
สัตว์ในตำนานกำลังบอกเราบางอย่าง
It's a proclamation.
มันคือการประกาศ
No, it's not. I've always been bad in communicating.
ไม่มันไม่ใช่. ฉันมักจะสื่อสารไม่ดี
That's true. I'm never able to have casual conversation.
นั่นเป็นความจริง ฉันไม่สามารถสนทนาแบบสบายๆ ได้เลย
Mythical Beast, the weather today is great.
สัตว์ในตำนาน วันนี้อากาศดีมาก
So what?
แล้วไง?
♫The alarm goes off. My name is Little Spider♫
♫นาฬิกาปลุกดับลง ฉันชื่อแมงมุมน้อย♫
EPISODE 19: I GUESS, THIS IS A CLASS REUNION? ♫The awakening survival skill♫
ตอนที่ 19: ฉันเดาว่านี่คือการรวมตัวของชั้นเรียน? ♫ทักษะการเอาชีวิตรอดที่ตื่นขึ้น♫
♫No obstacles can stop me♫
ตอนที่ 19: ฉันเดาว่านี่คือการรวมตัวของชั้นเรียน? ♫ไม่มีอุปสรรคใดหยุดฉันได้♫
♫Go! Dark clouds♫
♫ไป! เมฆมืด♫
♫Sometimes I pretend it's fate♫
♫บางครั้งฉันก็แสร้งทำเป็นว่าโชคชะตา♫
♫The 3-D perspective street that appears in the intersection of good and evil♫
♫ถนนมุมมอง 3 มิติ ที่ปรากฏอยู่ในทางแยกของความดีและความชั่ว♫
♫The labyrinth of nightmares is nothing to me♫
♫เขาวงกตแห่งฝันร้ายไม่มีความหมายสำหรับฉัน♫
♫Common sense isn't useful here♫
♫สามัญสำนึกไม่มีประโยชน์ที่นี่♫
♫Charging forward like a man is naive♫
♫ พุ่งไปข้างหน้าเหมือนผู้ชายไร้เดียงสา ♫
♫Because life isn't as easy as you think♫
♫เพราะชีวิตไม่ได้ง่ายอย่างที่คิด♫
♫It drives me forward♫
♫มันทำให้ฉันก้าวไปข้างหน้า♫
♫These hands created a brave me♫
♫มือเหล่านี้สร้างฉันให้กล้าหาญ♫
♫Excuse me, I'm the strongest!♫
♫ขอโทษนะ ฉันแข็งแกร่งที่สุด!♫
♫The violent and greedy spider is riding the wind♫
♫แมงมุมที่ดุร้ายและโลภกำลังขี่สายลม♫
♫The unpredictable waves♫
♫คลื่นที่คาดเดาไม่ได้♫
♫It's not the end yet♫
♫ ยังไม่จบ ♫
♫Use the fastest speed to pass through darkness♫
♫ใช้ความเร็วที่เร็วที่สุดเพื่อผ่านความมืด♫
♫Because we only live once♫
♫เพราะเรามีชีวิตอยู่เพียงครั้งเดียว♫
♫As long as we keep running forward♫
♫ตราบใดที่เรายังคงวิ่งไปข้างหน้า♫
♫Loosen the knot in your heart♫
♫ คลายปมในใจเธอ ♫
♫So you can jump right onto the next exciting stage♫
♫เพื่อให้คุณสามารถกระโดดไปยังเวทีที่น่าตื่นเต้นถัดไป♫
Isn't this a dead end?
นี่ไม่ใช่ทางตันเหรอ?
A Teleport Formation...
การสร้างเทเลพอร์ต...
The Elf Village is guarded by a powerful barrier.
หมู่บ้านเอลฟ์ได้รับการคุ้มกันโดยบาเรียอันทรงพลัง
Without this Teleport Formation, one can never enter.
หากไม่มีรูปแบบเทเลพอร์ตนี้ ก็ไม่มีใครสามารถเข้าไปได้
So this is the entrance of Elf Village.
นี่คือทางเข้าหมู่บ้านเอลฟ์
Please don't give this away. Let's go.
ได้โปรดอย่าทิ้งสิ่งนี้ไป ไปกันเถอะ.
Hold on a second. I brought them.
รอสักครู่. ฉันพาพวกเขามา
Name.
ชื่อ.
Filimøs Harrifenas.
Filimøs Harrifenas.
The daughter of the clan leader. Why did you bring humans here?
ลูกสาวของหัวหน้าเผ่า ทำไมคุณถึงพามนุษย์มาที่นี่?
They're reincarnations, the comrades of the true Warrior, those who help the Imperial Army.
พวกเขากำลังกลับชาติมาเกิด สหายของนักรบที่แท้จริง ผู้ช่วยเหลือกองทัพจักรวรรดิ
I know what's going on. But I can't let humans in the village.
ฉันรู้ว่าเกิดอะไรขึ้น แต่ฉันปล่อยให้มนุษย์อยู่ในหมู่บ้านไม่ได้
Why...
ทำไม...
Don't make me repeat my words. Please leave.
อย่าให้ฉันต้องพูดซ้ำ กรุณาออกไป.
Put your sword down.
วางดาบของคุณลง
You are...
คุณคือ...
Did you forget your father's face?
ลืมหน้าพ่อแล้วเหรอ?
Potimas?
โปติมัส?
This isn't real.
นี่ไม่ใช่ของจริง
Why are you...
ทำไมคุณ...
There are many ways to avoid death. In some extent, I won't die.
มีหลายวิธีที่จะหลีกเลี่ยงความตาย ในระดับหนึ่งฉันจะไม่ตาย
Welcome to the Elf Village.
ยินดีต้อนรับสู่หมู่บ้านเอลฟ์
Follow me. Although it's simple, I've prepared a welcoming banquet.
ปฏิบัติตามฉัน. แม้จะเรียบง่าย แต่ฉันก็เตรียมงานเลี้ยงต้อนรับไว้
How about the direction of the Imperial Army?
ทิศทางของกองทัพจักรวรรดิเป็นอย่างไร?
They haven't reached the barrier. They're still in the forest.
พวกเขายังไม่ถึงบาเรีย พวกเขายังอยู่ในป่า
How many of them?
มีกี่คน?
About 80,000 people.
ประมาณ 80,000 คน
80,000? They're fighting the Demon Clan with so few people?
80,000? พวกเขากำลังต่อสู้กับ Demon Clan กับคนไม่กี่คนเหรอ?
If Demon Clan knows about this, they will surely take advantage of this chance.
หาก Demon Clan รู้เรื่องนี้ พวกเขาจะฉวยโอกาสนี้อย่างแน่นอน
The tricky part is, the church has also contributed a lot to the troop.
ส่วนที่ยากก็คือ คริสตจักรได้มีส่วนช่วยเหลือกองทหารเป็นอย่างมาก
After Hugo was announced as the fake Warrior, their relation with the empire became firmer.
หลังจากที่ Hugo ได้รับการประกาศให้เป็นนักรบจอมปลอม ความสัมพันธ์ของพวกเขากับจักรวรรดิก็แน่นแฟ้นยิ่งขึ้น
I've prepared accommodation. After the meal, I'll bring you there.
ฉันได้เตรียมที่พักไว้แล้ว หลังอาหารฉันจะพาคุณไปที่นั่น
Thank you for your care.
ขอบคุณสำหรับการดูแลของคุณ
Tomorrow you can go see your friends.
พรุ่งนี้คุณสามารถไปหาเพื่อนของคุณ
Friends?
เพื่อน?
The reincarnations.
การกลับชาติมาเกิด
Reincarnations?
การกลับชาติมาเกิด?
What do you think?
คุณคิดอย่างไร?
Think what?
คิดอะไร?
Potimas. The house is ready as well. He's too well prepared.
โปติมา. บ้านก็พร้อมเช่นกัน เขาพร้อมเกินไป
Yes. As if he knew that we're coming.
ใช่. ราวกับว่าเขารู้ว่าเรากำลังมา
That old man is suspicious.
ชายชราคนนั้นสงสัย
We better be careful.
เราควรระวังไว้ดีกว่า
Same goes to the teacher.
เดียวกันกับครู
What?
อะไร?
We shouldn't trust her so much. She might be giving away our whereabouts.
เราไม่ควรไว้ใจเธอมากนัก เธออาจจะบอกที่อยู่ของเรา
How is it possible?
มันเป็นไปได้ยังไงกัน?
Wasn't she also shocked when she saw Potimas?
เธอไม่ตกใจเมื่อเห็นโปติมาสด้วยหรือ?
She might have been putting on a show.
เธออาจจะกำลังแสดงละครอยู่
Teacher, how many hours do we have to walk?
ครูคะ เราต้องเดินกี่ชั่วโมงคะ?
We're almost there. Elf Village is very huge.
เราเกือบจะอยู่ที่นั่นแล้ว หมู่บ้านเอลฟ์มีขนาดใหญ่มาก
Going from one end to another requires a day.
การไปจากปลายข้างหนึ่งไปอีกปลายหนึ่งต้องใช้เวลาหนึ่งวัน
A barrier that covers such a large area.
สิ่งกีดขวางที่ครอบคลุมพื้นที่ขนาดใหญ่ดังกล่าว
It seems you have very powerful magic.
ดูเหมือนว่าคุณมีเวทย์มนตร์ที่ทรงพลังมาก
Thanks to this barrier, Elf Village hasn't been attacked until now.
ต้องขอบคุณบาเรียนี้ หมู่บ้านเอลฟ์จึงยังไม่ถูกโจมตีมาจนถึงตอนนี้
It's said, we don't even have to be afraid of the Queen Taratect's attack.
ว่ากันว่า เราไม่ต้องกลัวการจู่โจมของราชินีทาราเทคด้วยซ้ำ
Such a strong barrier. Can Hugo destroy it?
อุปสรรคที่แข็งแกร่งเช่นนี้ Hugo สามารถทำลายมันได้หรือไม่?
No one can guarantee that it won't be destroyed.
ไม่มีใครรับประกันได้ว่าจะไม่ถูกทำลาย
Are you talking about the killer's move of Hugo?
คุณกำลังพูดถึงการเคลื่อนไหวของ Hugo ของนักฆ่าหรือไม่?
I don't know either. This barrier is well-known.
ฉันก็ไม่รู้เหมือนกัน อุปสรรคนี้เป็นที่รู้จักกันดี
If one isn't confident to break through it...
ถ้าใครไม่มั่นใจในการทำลายล้าง...
We can see it now.
เราสามารถดูได้แล้ว
That's the protected area of reincarnations.
นั่นคือพื้นที่คุ้มครองของการกลับชาติมาเกิด
Teacher, you're back.
คุณครูกลับมาแล้ว
Yes, I'm back.
ใช่ ฉันกลับมาแล้ว
Are these three the new victims?
สามคนนี้เป็นเหยื่อรายใหม่หรือเปล่า?
They're not victims.
พวกเขาไม่ใช่เหยื่อ
Our views are different.
มุมมองของเราต่างกัน
At least to me, you're the perpetrator.
อย่างน้อยสำหรับฉัน คุณคือผู้กระทำความผิด
Whatever. What's their names?
อะไรก็ได้ ชื่อของพวกเขาคืออะไร?
That feeling... Am I the only one who thinks about that person?
ความรู้สึกนั้น... ฉันเป็นคนเดียวที่คิดถึงคนๆ นั้นหรือเปล่า?
To be honest, me too.
พูดตามตรงฉันด้วย
Me too.
ฉันด้วย.
I'm not talking about the name of this world, but the other world.
ฉันไม่ได้พูดถึงชื่อของโลกนี้ แต่เป็นอีกโลกหนึ่ง
It's obvious, right? I'm Shinohara Mirei.
มันชัดเจนใช่มั้ย? ฉันชิโนฮาระ มิเรอิ
Indeed.
แท้จริงแล้ว
I'm Yamada Shunsuke.
ฉันยามาดะ ชุนสุเกะ
I'm Ooshima Kanata.
ฉันโอชิมะ คานาตะ
Hold on. You're Ooshima?
เดี๋ยวก่อน คุณโอชิมะ?
Indeed.
แท้จริงแล้ว
What kind of reaction is that? That's rude.
ปฏิกิริยาแบบนั้นคืออะไร? ที่หยาบคาย
Sorry. That was unexpected.
ขอโทษ นั่นเป็นสิ่งที่ไม่คาดคิด
Hey, we've told you our names. Shouldn't you tell us yours?
เฮ้ เราบอกชื่อของเราให้คุณแล้ว คุณไม่ควรจะบอกเราของคุณ?
That was rude indeed. I'm Kudo Sachi.
นั่นเป็นสิ่งที่หยาบคายอย่างแน่นอน ฉันคูโดะ ซาจิ
Indeed... The chairman.
แน่นอน...ท่านประธาน.
Shinohara, why do you look so much like you in the previous life?
ชิโนฮาระ ทำไมชาติก่อนหน้าเหมือนเธอจัง
Who knows? Perhaps I was loathe to let my beauty die.
ใครจะรู้? บางทีฉันก็เกลียดที่จะปล่อยให้ความงามของฉันตาย
Don't talk to yourself.
อย่าพูดกับตัวเอง
You're as straightforward as ever.
คุณตรงไปตรงมาเหมือนเคย
Mirei, really?
มิเรย์จริงเหรอ?
Is that her?
นั่นคือเธอ?
Could that be Ai and Kumi?
นั่นอาจเป็น Ai และ Kumi?
That's right!
ถูกตัอง!
It's Mirei! Long time no see.
มิเรอิ! ไม่ได้เจอกันนานเลยนะ.
We've died once. That was indeed long.
เราเคยตายไปแล้วครั้งหนึ่ง นั่นยาวจริงๆ
By the way, they're Yamada and Ooshima.
อย่างไรก็ตาม พวกเขาคือยามาดะและโอชิมะ
You're lying. Ooshima?
คุณโกหก. โอชิมะ?
Impossible.
เป็นไปไม่ได้
-Right? -Didn't I say that was rude?
-ขวา? - ฉันไม่ได้บอกว่าหยาบคายเหรอ?
Let's not talk standing.
อย่ายืนคุยกัน
Our work today is complete.
งานของเราวันนี้เสร็จเรียบร้อยแล้ว
-You may rest now. -It's complete. Yay!
- คุณพักผ่อนได้แล้ว -ครบแล้ว. เย้!
Teacher, you want to come? Although we don't welcome you.
ครูคุณต้องการมา? แม้ว่าเราจะไม่ต้อนรับคุณ
That's right. You finally got together. If I'm around, you won't be happy.
ถูกตัอง. ในที่สุดคุณก็อยู่ด้วยกัน ถ้าฉันอยู่ใกล้คุณจะไม่มีความสุข
I'm not coming.
ฉันไม่มา
Weren't Oka and Kudo close back then?
ตอนนั้น Oka และ Kudo ไม่สนิทกันเหรอ?
Yes.
ใช่.
Let's go.
ไปกันเถอะ.
Let's go, Shun.
ไปกันเถอะชุน
Shun and Kanata?
ชุนกับคานาตะ?
Could you be Ogi?
คุณสามารถเป็น Ogi?
Yes, Ogiwara Kenichi. Long time no see. You recognise people well.
ใช่ โอกิวาระ เคนอิจิ ไม่ได้เจอกันนานเลยนะ. คุณรู้จักคนได้ดี
No one is as enthusiastic as you.
ไม่มีใครกระตือรือร้นเท่าคุณ
Let's introduce ourselves, our previous selves.
มาแนะนำตัวกัน ตัวก่อนหน้าของเรา
Aikawa.
ส่ง.
Maki Shouwato.
มากิ โชวาโตะ.
Furuta Mio.
ฟุรุตะ มิโอะ.
Nanase Chie.
นานาเสะ เจีย.
Segawa Shuuko.
เซกาว่า ชูโกะ.
Temarikawa Saki.
เทมาริคาวะ ซากิ.
Tsushima Dai.
สึชิมะได.
Tagawa Kunihiko.
ทากาวะ คุนิฮิโกะ.
Kushitani Asaka.
คุชิทานิ อาซากะ.
They just arrived recently. They were adventurers.
พวกเขาเพิ่งมาถึงเมื่อไม่นานนี้เอง พวกเขาเป็นนักผจญภัย
Ijima Aiko.
อิจิมะ ไอโกะ.
Tonooka Kumiko.
โทนูกะ คูมิโกะ.
Yes, yes.
ใช่ ๆ.
That's everyone.
นั่นคือทุกคน
A total of 13?
ทั้งหมด 13?
Two more than Oka told us. Are those Tagawa and Asaka?
มากกว่าที่ Oka บอกเราสองคน พวกนั้นคือทากาวะกับอาซากะเหรอ?
By the way...
ยังไงซะ...
Kanata, why did you become such a beauty?
คานาตะ ทำไมเธอกลายเป็นคนสวยอย่างนี้ล่ะ?
I'm asking that too.
ฉันก็ถามแบบนั้นเหมือนกัน
Am I the only one that has a different gender?
ฉันเป็นคนเดียวที่มีเพศต่างกันหรือไม่?
At least you're still a human. I'm a monster.
อย่างน้อยคุณก็ยังเป็นมนุษย์ ฉันเป็นสัตว์ประหลาด
So what?
แล้วไง?
Stop it.
หยุดนะ.
Natsume wants to attack us?
นัตสึเมะต้องการโจมตีเราเหรอ?
Yes.
ใช่.
Not only Natsume.
ไม่ใช่แค่นัตสึเมะ
They have Yuri as well. No, I mean Hasebe.
มียูริด้วย ไม่ ฉันหมายถึงฮาเซเบะ
Yuika?
ยูกะ?
She seems to be brainwashed.
ดูเหมือนเธอจะถูกล้างสมอง
Wouldn't the elves tell you about the outside news?
พวกเอลฟ์จะไม่บอกคุณเกี่ยวกับข่าวภายนอกเหรอ?
Yes. The elves try not to be related to us.
ใช่. เอลฟ์พยายามที่จะไม่เกี่ยวข้องกับเรา
What's with the silence?
เป็นอะไรกับความเงียบ?
No. Because I can't associate such a beauty with Kanata.
ไม่ เพราะฉันไม่สามารถเชื่อมโยงความงามกับคานาตะได้
No, sorry.
ไม่ล่ะขอบคุณ.
I find it hard to converse.
ฉันพบว่ามันยากที่จะพูดคุย
Okay. If you mind, I shall move to the girls' side.
ตกลง. ถ้าคุณรังเกียจ ฉันจะย้ายไปอยู่ฝั่งผู้หญิง
Please stay here.
กรุณาอยู่ที่นี่
Well, what do you think about this village?
คิดยังไงกับหมู่บ้านนี้
It feels like we're kidnapped here.
รู้สึกเหมือนเราถูกลักพาตัวมาที่นี่
Kidnapped?
ลักพาตัว?
Although our situations were different, basically we were sold by our parents.
แม้ว่าสถานการณ์ของเราจะแตกต่างกัน แต่โดยพื้นฐานแล้วเราถูกพ่อแม่ขาย
It was worse for Temarikawa Saki, who was basically abducted here.
เทมาริคาวะ ซากิ ผู้ซึ่งถูกลักพาตัวมาที่นี่นั้นเลวร้ายยิ่งกว่า
To a certain extent, this is expected.
คาดว่าจะได้ในระดับหนึ่ง
Didn't I mention it? The teacher is the perpetrator.
ฉันไม่ได้พูดถึงมันเหรอ? ครูคือผู้กระทำความผิด
Don't you say such things as killing isn't allowed.
อย่าพูดว่าห้ามฆ่า
Haven't you killed many people as well?
คุณไม่ได้ฆ่าคนจำนวนมากเช่นกัน?
She said she's protecting us, but she's just putting us on house arrest.
เธอบอกว่าเธอกำลังปกป้องเรา แต่เธอแค่กักขังเราไว้ที่บ้าน
Besides giving us resources, she doesn't care about us.
นอกจากให้ทรัพยากรแก่เราแล้ว เธอยังไม่สนใจเราอีกด้วย
I can't trust the elves and the teacher.
ฉันไม่สามารถไว้ใจพวกเอลฟ์และครูได้
Does anyone know about Kyouya? Sasajima Kyouya.
ใครรู้จักเคียวยะบ้าง? ซาซาจิมะ เคียวยะ.
Sasajima Kyouya?
ซาซาจิมะ เคียวยะ?
We don't know.
เราไม่รู้
What about Tagawa and Kushitani? Don't adventurers go around?
ทากาวะและคุชิทานิล่ะ? นักผจญภัยอย่าไปไหนมาไหน?
No. We don't know either.
ไม่ เราก็ไม่รู้เหมือนกัน
I see.
ฉันเห็น.
We've met almost all the reincarnations.
เราได้พบกับการเกิดใหม่เกือบทั้งหมด
There are two left.
เหลืออยู่สองตัว
Yes.
ใช่.
The teacher mentioned four are dead. Should we trust that?
ครูกล่าวถึงสี่เสียชีวิต เราควรเชื่ออย่างนั้นหรือ?
Kyouya, where are you and what are you doing?
เคียวยะ นายอยู่ที่ไหน ทำอะไรอยู่?
Ohts is protesting?
โอ๊ตประท้วง?
They want us to give up the taratect.
พวกเขาต้องการให้เราเลิกทาราเท็ค
They claimed these are all their rights.
พวกเขาอ้างว่านี่เป็นสิทธิ์ทั้งหมดของพวกเขา
What nonsense. A wild monster doesn't belong to anyone.
ไร้สาระอะไร สัตว์ประหลาดป่าไม่ได้เป็นของใคร
Father has been working very hard recently.
พ่อทำงานหนักมากเมื่อเร็ว ๆ นี้
The monster that lives in the forest of our territory is to be blamed.
สัตว์ประหลาดที่อาศัยอยู่ในป่าในดินแดนของเราจะต้องถูกตำหนิ
Why did this happen?
ทำไมสิ่งนี้จึงเกิดขึ้น?
The taratect, the Nightmare of the Labyrinth, destroyed the fortress of Ohts.
taratect ฝันร้ายของเขาวงกต ทำลายป้อมปราการของ Ohts
They want it punished.
พวกเขาต้องการให้ลงโทษ
What a troublesome fellow.
What a troublesome fellow.
I wonder why it's known as the Mythical Beast.
I wonder why it's known as the Mythical Beast.
People of other countries keep coming to negotiate with father.
People of other countries keep coming to negotiate with father.
Give it up to avoid risk or something like that.
Give it up to avoid risk or something like that.
How are you planning to reply?
How are you planning to reply?
To sincerely and euphemistically tell them that it doesn't belong to us.
To sincerely and euphemistically tell them that it doesn't belong to us.
Master, the guest...
Master, the guest...
I'm not seeing any guest today. Send them away.
I'm not seeing any guest today. Send them away.
It won't take long.
It won't take long.
I'm the clan leader of the elves. My name is Potimas.
I'm the clan leader of the elves. My name is Potimas.
Elf? This is my first time seeing one in person.
Elf? This is my first time seeing one in person.
The clan leader of the elves.
The clan leader of the elves.
Sorry for the sudden visit.
Sorry for the sudden visit.
It's okay. You came all the way to visit.
It's okay. You came all the way to visit.
It's my pleasure.
It's my pleasure.
May I know what you are here for?
May I know what you are here for?
Nothing much. I just want to have a look at this widely known Mythical Beast.
Nothing much. I just want to have a look at this widely known Mythical Beast.
You have a very great Mythical Beast.
You have a very great Mythical Beast.
It's giving me a lot of trouble recently.
It's giving me a lot of trouble recently.
That's unexpected.
That's unexpected.
He's looking this way.
He's looking this way.
Your daughter is so cute. What's her name?
ลูกสาวของคุณน่ารักมาก เธอชื่ออะไร
She's called Sophia.
เธอชื่อโซเฟีย
Sophia.
โซเฟีย
I see.
ฉันเห็น.
That spider is a guardian Ariel sent you. Not to be underestimated.
แมงมุมตัวนั้นเป็นผู้พิทักษ์ที่แอเรียลส่งคุณมา ไม่ควรประมาท
What? Ariel? Is that a detergent or softener?
อะไร? เอเรียล? นั่นผงซักฟอกหรือน้ำยาปรับผ้านุ่ม?
Ariel has noticed the existence of the reincarnations. Is that right?
เอเรียลสังเกตเห็นการมีอยู่ของการกลับชาติมาเกิด นั่นถูกต้องใช่ไหม?
Master Potimas.
อาจารย์โปติมาศ.
Excuse me. She's too cute. I can't wait to see her appearance in the future.
ขออนุญาต. เธอน่ารักเกินไป ฉันแทบรอไม่ไหวที่จะได้เห็นรูปร่างหน้าตาของเธอในอนาคต
What's wrong with that guy? This doesn't feel good.
มีอะไรผิดปกติกับผู้ชายคนนั้น? นี่รู้สึกไม่ดีเลย
WISDOM
ปัญญา
It's the Devil!
มันคือปีศาจ!
Oh no, she's coming my way! Oh no!
ไม่นะ เธอกำลังมาทางฉัน! ไม่นะ!
This fellow is scary!
คนนี้น่ากลัว!
Should I run?
ฉันควรจะวิ่ง?
By the way, where is mother?
สรุปว่าแม่อยู่ไหน?
"WISDOM" She's at the Bottom Stratum of Great Elroe Labyrinth.
"WISDOM" เธออยู่ที่ชั้นล่างสุดของ Great Elroe Labyrinth
"IDENTIFICATION" Hello, mother. Are you feeling alright?
"บัตรประจำตัว" สวัสดีแม่ คุณสบายดีไหม
QUEEN TARATECT. WEAKENING. LEVEL 89. Her condition is horrible.
ควีนทาราเทก. อ่อนแอ ระดับ 89 อาการของเธอแย่มาก
Her ability values are averagely 6,000.
ค่าความสามารถของเธออยู่ที่ 6,000 โดยเฉลี่ย
They're about 70% worse than before.
พวกเขาแย่กว่าเมื่อก่อนประมาณ 70%
That's right. Discount auction before closing begins now!
ถูกตัอง. ประมูลลดก่อนปิด เริ่มตอนนี้!
Well done, parallel wills.
ทำได้ดีมาก พินัยกรรมคู่ขนาน
Body!
ร่างกาย!
Because of all your effort, mother's ability values have reduced.
เพราะความพยายามทั้งหมดของคุณ ค่าความสามารถของแม่จึงลดลง
Thank you!
ขอขอบคุณ!
In comparison, I'm energetic now while Devil isn't around,
ในการเปรียบเทียบ ตอนนี้ฉันมีพลังในขณะที่เดวิลไม่อยู่
here's the time to win!
ถึงเวลาที่จะชนะแล้ว!
Let's go to the Bottom Stratum of Great Elroe Labyrinth.
ไปที่ชั้นล่างของ Great Elroe Labyrinth กันเถอะ
I'm going to surpass you now.
ฉันจะแซงหน้าคุณเดี๋ยวนี้
No. I can't surpass you in size. She looks huge in person.
ไม่ ฉันไม่สามารถเกินขนาดคุณได้ เธอดูยิ่งใหญ่ในตัว
What's with this feeling of oppression?
ความรู้สึกกดขี่นี้คืออะไร?
Did she really become weaker? It's so scary.
เธออ่อนแอลงจริงหรือ? มันน่ากลัวมาก
I can't hold back.
ฉันไม่สามารถถือกลับ
I'm twice as fast as mother. It's more than enough... Weird.
ฉันเร็วเป็นสองเท่าของแม่ มันเกินพอแล้ว... แปลก
More than enough... Why can't I move?
เกินพอ...ทำไมขยับไม่ได้?
Seriously?
อย่างจริงจัง?
Mother's silks. A high level silk skill.
ผ้าไหมแม่. ทักษะสายไหมระดับสูง
Is that a trap?
นั่นคือกับดัก?
Hold on a second.
รอสักครู่.
I want to heal my legs first.
ฉันต้องการรักษาขาของฉันก่อน
Wait for me.
รอฉันด้วย.
I'll be dead if I'm hit.
ฉันจะตายถ้าฉันถูกตี
Oh no. The silks!
ไม่นะ. สายไหม!
What?
อะไร?
Seriously? Did she spit silks everywhere?
อย่างจริงจัง? เธอคายไหมทุกที่?
So strong.
แข็งแรงมาก
What should I do? Teleport?
ฉันควรทำอย่างไรดี? เทเลพอร์ต?
I can't use magic in time. In this case...
ฉันใช้เวทย์มนตร์ไม่ทัน ในกรณีนี้...
It appears. The head of the spider.
มันจะปรากฏขึ้น. หัวของแมงมุม
How about surrendering obediently?
จะยอมแพ้อย่างเชื่อฟังได้อย่างไร?
"SO I'M A SPIDER, SO WHAT?" Oh no. She's doing that again.
"ฉันเป็นแมงมุม แล้วไง" ไม่นะ. เธอทำแบบนั้นอีกแล้ว
A revolving lantern appeared.
โคมหมุนได้ปรากฏขึ้น
It's my fault to think I could defeat her once she turns weak.
เป็นความผิดของฉันที่คิดว่าฉันสามารถเอาชนะเธอได้เมื่อเธออ่อนแอ
Even when mother's soul is being gnawed... Even when it's desperate,
ต่อให้วิญญาณของแม่ถูกแทะ... แม้จะสิ้นหวัง
she keeps fighting and never give up.
เธอยังคงต่อสู้และไม่ยอมแพ้
I want to inherit the will power of my mother.
ฉันต้องการสืบทอดอำนาจเจตจำนงของแม่ของฉัน
I can't be defeated by her.
ฉันแพ้เธอไม่ได้
At least I should let mother know that I'm a strong enemy that fights until the end.
อย่างน้อยฉันก็ควรให้แม่รู้ว่าฉันคือศัตรูตัวฉกาจที่ต่อสู้จนถึงที่สุด
Okay. The last strike before death.
ตกลง. ครั้งสุดท้ายก่อนตาย.
This is the determination.
นี่คือความมุ่งมั่น
What?
อะไร?
The previous person in charge of magic, long time no see.
คนเดิมที่ดูแลเรื่องเวทมนตร์ ไม่เจอกันนานเลย
But even if you're back now, you'll be killed like me.
แต่แม้ว่าคุณจะกลับมาตอนนี้ คุณจะถูกฆ่าเหมือนฉัน
At least you should survive.
อย่างน้อยคุณควรอยู่รอด
I've received your encouragement.
ฉันได้รับกำลังใจของคุณแล้ว
What happened?
เกิดอะไรขึ้น?
I feel like I'm full of power.
ฉันรู้สึกเหมือนฉันเต็มไปด้วยพลัง
Where do you think mother's missing ability values went to?
คุณคิดว่าค่าความสามารถที่หายไปของแม่ไปที่ไหน?
I don't know.
ฉันไม่รู้
We ate mother's mental body. Mental body is soul.
เรากินกายใจของแม่ กายจิตก็คือจิต
Ability values and skills are the strength of souls.
ค่าความสามารถและทักษะคือความแข็งแกร่งของจิตวิญญาณ
What does it mean?
มันหมายความว่าอะไร?
That means, mother's strength
แปลว่า พลังของแม่
will be transferred to us who eaten her soul, right?
จะถูกโอนมาให้เราที่กินวิญญาณของเธอใช่ไหม?
That means, the missing ability values of hers is used to increase my ability?
หมายความว่า ค่าความสามารถที่หายไปของเธอถูกใช้เพื่อเพิ่มความสามารถของฉัน?
Correct!
แก้ไข!
Alright.
เอาล่ะ
Fight back!
สู้กลับ!
So awesome!
ดีมาก ๆ!
The healing magic is fast as well.
เวทมนตร์แห่งการรักษานั้นรวดเร็วเช่นกัน
ZANA HOROWA. NAMELESS. LEVEL 24.
ซาน่า โฮโรว่า. นิรนาม ระดับ 24
What is this?
นี่คืออะไร?
This value is odd. I've became very strong.
ค่านี้เป็นค่าคี่ ฉันแข็งแกร่งขึ้นมาก
Isn't this the privilege of the protagonists of mangas?
นี่เป็นสิทธิพิเศษของตัวเอกของการ์ตูนไม่ใช่หรือ?
Just kill her first, then we will talk.
ฆ่าเธอก่อนแล้วค่อยคุยกัน
Mother, you're great. Goodbye.
แม่คุณเยี่ยมมาก ลาก่อน
Everyone, thank you. You're back!
ทุกคน ขอบคุณนะ คุณกลับมาแล้ว!
Let me tell you.
ให้ฉันบอกคุณ.
What?
อะไร?
The previous person in charge of body is gone.
คนก่อนหน้าที่ดูแลร่างกายหายไป
Where is she?
เธออยู่ที่ไหน?
At the Devil's.
ที่เดวิลส์.
Devil? Why?
ปีศาจ? ทำไม?
When mother and Devil contacted, the channel was opened.
เมื่อแม่กับมารติดต่อมา ช่องก็เปิด
She went to attack Devil through that channel.
เธอไปโจมตี Devil ผ่านช่องนั้น
Could she come back?
เธอกลับมาได้ไหม
Who knows? Maybe not.
ใครจะรู้? อาจจะไม่.
Because there's no connection between Devil and I.
เพราะไม่มีความเชื่อมโยงระหว่างเดวิลกับฉัน
That's right.
ถูกตัอง.
WISDOM
ปัญญา
Oh no, Devil is coming this way.
ไม่นะ เดวิลกำลังมาทางนี้
Retreat!
ล่าถอย!
Goodbye, the previous person in charge of body.
ลาก่อน ผู้ที่เคยดูแลร่างกาย
Body.
ร่างกาย.
I will never forget you.
ฉันจะไม่มีวันลืมเธอ.
♫This is annoying. I'm sure I won♫
♫นี่มันน่ารำคาญ ฉันแน่ใจว่าฉันชนะ♫
♫Weak one (swallow it) Strong ones (Exhausted). Take it as nutrition♫
♫ตัวอ่อน (กลืนเข้าไป) ตัวที่แข็งแรง (หมดแรง) ใช้เป็นสารอาหาร ♫
♫"Again! Again!" What a boring game♫
♫"อีกครั้ง!อีกครั้ง!" ช่างเป็นเกมที่น่าเบื่อ♫
♫Don't look down at life♫
♫อย่าดูถูกชีวิต♫
♫Fooled. I knew your intelligence is wrong♫
♫โง่เขลา ฉันรู้ว่าสติปัญญาของคุณผิด♫
♫Tell me how it feels to be fooled by an inferior animal♫
♫บอกฉันทีว่ารู้สึกอย่างไรที่ถูกสัตว์ที่ด้อยกว่าหลอกมา♫
♫I'm still happy over your misery today. I shall start eating now♫
♫ฉันยังคงมีความสุขกับความทุกข์ยากของคุณในวันนี้ ฉันจะเริ่มกินแล้ว ♫
♫Unreasonable, unlucky, so what?♫
♫ไร้เหตุผล โชคร้าย แล้วไงล่ะ♫
♫I want to try my best to live♫
♫ฉันอยากจะพยายามใช้ชีวิตให้ดีที่สุด♫
♫Succeeded. I almost got all of you♫
♫ประสบความสำเร็จ เกือบได้ทุกคนแล้ว ♫
♫Silk control. Venomous fangs. Sure-win strategy. Watch it♫
♫ควบคุมไหม เขี้ยวพิษ. กลยุทธ์ที่ชนะแน่นอน ดูมัน♫
♫Victory! No one can stop me♫
♫ชัยชนะ! ไม่มีใครหยุดฉันได้ ♫
♫Despite the failed reincarnation, I want to keep living♫
♫ถึงแม้ว่าการเกิดใหม่จะล้มเหลว ฉันก็ยังอยากมีชีวิตอยู่ต่อไป♫
♫Defeat! Great! Spider! Good!♫
♫พ่ายแพ้! เยี่ยมมาก! แมงมุม! ดี!♫
♫Defeat! No problem! Spider's style! (Die, die die)♫
♫พ่ายแพ้! ไม่มีปัญหา! สไตล์แมงมุม! (ตาย ตาย ตาย) ♫
Unforgivable.
ยกโทษให้ไม่ได้
It seems to be a tough battle.
ดูเหมือนว่าจะเป็นการต่อสู้ที่ยากลำบาก
What's the matter? You're being nosy. That's a violation of the agreement.
เกิดอะไรขึ้น? คุณกำลังเสือก นั่นเป็นการละเมิดข้อตกลง
That's the agreement between my master and you.
นั่นคือข้อตกลงระหว่างเจ้านายของฉันกับคุณ
I have to obey to all the orders of my master. He didn't say I can't have conflict with you.
ฉันต้องเชื่อฟังคำสั่งทั้งหมดของนาย เขาไม่ได้บอกว่าฉันไม่สามารถขัดแย้งกับคุณ
Sophistry. So what?
ความซับซ้อน แล้วไง?
Don't you think it's time to obsolete?
คุณไม่คิดว่ามันถึงเวลาที่จะล้าสมัย?
What do you mean?
คุณหมายถึงอะไร
A new trend is coming.
เทรนด์ใหม่กำลังมา
As ancient mythical beasts, it's about time for us to leave this world.
ในฐานะสัตว์ในตำนานโบราณ ถึงเวลาแล้วที่เราจะจากโลกนี้ไป
There's a strong one who defeated our comrades.
มีผู้แข็งแกร่งคนหนึ่งที่เอาชนะสหายของเราได้
She isn't someone you can harm now.
เธอไม่ใช่คนที่คุณสามารถทำร้ายได้ในตอนนี้
I have to say, my mood is horrible now.
ฉันต้องบอกว่าอารมณ์ของฉันตอนนี้แย่มาก
If you keep nagging, I'll make you disappear.
หากคุณยังคงจู้จี้ ฉันจะทำให้คุณหายไป
A strong one is always respectable.
ผู้แข็งแกร่งย่อมน่ายกย่องเสมอ
I told you to shut up!
ฉันบอกให้หุบปาก!
SO I'M A SPIDER, SO WHAT? NEXT EPISODE: IS IT, MY FAULT?
ฉันเป็นแมงมุม แล้วไง ตอนต่อไป: มันเป็นความผิดของฉันเหรอ?
STAY TUNE
คอยติดตาม